So if you are considering
going into experimental physics...
(Leonard:)...my door is always open.
(Leonard:)Again, I'm sorry that the demonstration
didn't quite work out.
(Leonard:)Now we know what happens...
(Leonard:)...when you accidentally spill peach
Snapple into a helium-neon laser.
The short answer is don't.
(Leonard:)Now to tell you about
the Theoretical Physics Department...
(Leonard:)...is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Leonard:)- Dr. Cooper?
SHELDON: Forget it.
(Leonard:)Excuse me.
(Leonard:)- Sheldon, we both agreed to do this.
SHELDON: It's a waste of time.
I might as well explain thermodynamics
to a bunch of Labradoodles.
(Leonard:)If you don't do this,
I won't take you to the comic-book store.
(Sheldon(entering):)Hello.
(Sheldon(entering):)Nice work with the laser, by the way.